<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GuessPic!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_choice">ChoiceActivity</string>

    <string name="soon">Скоро!</string>

    <string name="about">О приложении</string>

    <string name="about_GuessPic_1">Игра «Угадай картинку!»</string>
    <string name="about_GuessPic_2">Версия 1 (BETA)</string>
    <string name="about_GuessPic_3">Все изображения распространяются по лицензиям Creative Commons, Open Database License, Open Government Licence, GNU FDL, разрешающие модификацию и распространение
    в коммерческих целях. Некоторые изображения находятся в общественном достоянии. Аттрибуция на каждое изображение присутствует.
        \n\nАвтор / Author: Nikolai Kopa
        \n\nКонтакт / Contact me: nikolai.kopa@gmail.com
        \n\nНиже представлены сторонние библиотеки, используемые в этом приложении ↓
    </string>

    <string name="about_Fresco_1">Fresco</string>
    <string name="about_Fresco_2">BSD License</string>
    <string name="about_Fresco_3">For Fresco software
    \n\nCopyright (c) 2015-present, Facebook, Inc. All rights reserved.
    \n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
    are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
    \n\n* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
    list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    \n\n* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
    this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
    and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    \n\n* Neither the name Facebook nor the names of its contributors may be used to
    endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific
    prior written permission.
    \n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND
    ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
    WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
    DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR
    ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
    (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
    LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
    ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
    (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
    SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    \n\nAdditional Grant of Patent Rights Version 2
    \n\n"Software" means the Fresco software distributed by Facebook, Inc.
    \n\nFacebook, Inc. ("Facebook") hereby grants to each recipient of the Software
    ("you") a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive, irrevocable
    (subject to the termination provision below) license under any Necessary
    Claims, to make, have made, use, sell, offer to sell, import, and otherwise
    transfer the Software. For avoidance of doubt, no license is granted under
    Facebook’s rights in any patent claims that are infringed by (i) modifications
    to the Software made by you or any third party or (ii) the Software in
    combination with any software or other technology.
    \n\nThe license granted hereunder will terminate, automatically and without notice,
    if you (or any of your subsidiaries, corporate affiliates or agents) initiate
    directly or indirectly, or take a direct financial interest in, any Patent
    Assertion: (i) against Facebook or any of its subsidiaries or corporate
    affiliates, (ii) against any party if such Patent Assertion arises in whole or
    in part from any software, technology, product or service of Facebook or any of
    its subsidiaries or corporate affiliates, or (iii) against any party relating
    to the Software. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if Facebook or any of its
    subsidiaries or corporate affiliates files a lawsuit alleging patent
    infringement against you in the first instance, and you respond by filing a
    patent infringement counterclaim in that lawsuit against that party that is
    unrelated to the Software, the license granted hereunder will not terminate
    under section (i) of this paragraph due to such counterclaim.
    \n\nA "Necessary Claim" is a claim of a patent owned by Facebook that is
    necessarily infringed by the Software standing alone.
    \n\nA "Patent Assertion" is any lawsuit or other action alleging direct, indirect,
    or contributory infringement or inducement to infringe any patent, including a
    cross-claim or counterclaim.
    </string>

    <string name="about_Retrofit_1">Retrofit</string>
    <string name="about_Retrofit_2">Apache License, Version 2.0</string>
    <string name="about_Retrofit_3">Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.
    \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at
    \n\n\thttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.</string>

    <string name="about_Gson_1">GSON</string>
    <string name="about_Gson_2">Apache License, Version 2.0</string>
    <string name="about_Gson_3">Copyright 2008 Google Inc.
    \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at
    \n\n\thttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.</string>

    <string name="about_FacebookSDK_1">Facebook SDK for Android</string>
    <string name="about_FacebookSDK_2">Facebook Platform License</string>
    <string name="about_FacebookSDK_3">Copyright (c) 2014-present, Facebook, Inc. All rights reserved.
    \n\nYou are hereby granted a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free license to use,
    copy, modify, and distribute this software in source code or binary form for use
    in connection with the web services and APIs provided by Facebook.
    \n\nAs with any software that integrates with the Facebook platform, your use of
    this software is subject to the Facebook Developer Principles and Policies
    [http://developers.facebook.com/policy/]. This copyright notice shall be
    included in all copies or substantial portions of the software.
    \n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
    IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS
    FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR
    COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER
    IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN
    CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>

    <string name="about_VKAndroidSDK_1">VK Android SDK</string>
    <string name="about_VKAndroidSDK_2">The MIT License (MIT)</string>
    <string name="about_VKAndroidSDK_3">Copyright (c) 2014 VK.com
    \n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of
    this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in
    the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to
    use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of
    the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so,
    subject to the following conditions:
    \n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
    copies or substantial portions of the Software.
    \n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
    IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS
    FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR
    COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER
    IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN
    CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>

    <string name="about_font_1">Krabuler Font</string>
    <string name="about_font_2">Russian Fonts License</string>
    <string name="about_font_3">Действие данной лицензии автоматически вступает силу после
    установки шрифта на компьютер или любое другое оборудование.
    \n\nШрифт можно использовать в личных и коммерческих.
    \n\nИсключение. Телевизионные компании и анимационные/
    мультипликационные студии (средства массовой информации)
    должны заключить отдельный договор на расширенную
    неисключительную лицензию позволяющую использовать шрифты
    в своих материалах (аудиовизуальной продукции). Использование
    шрифтов для телевизионных компаний и анимационных/
    мультипликационных студий предоставляется на платной основе.
    \n\nЗапрещается создавать на основе шрифта его копии или аналоги
    для личного/коммерческого использования или дальнейшего
    распространения.
    \n\nШрифт и сопутствующие материалы защищены авторским правом
    и содержат конфиденциальную информацию и коммерческую
    тайну относящуюся к разработчику (russianfonts.ru) выпустившему
    шрифт. Несанкционированное копирование, модификация
    категорически запрещено. Вы можете быть привлечены к
    юридической ответственности за любое нарушение авторских прав
    интеллектуальной собственности обусловленного несоблюдением
    данного соглашения (ГК РФ ст. 1259 пункт 1).
    \n\nРазработчик не гарантирует бесперебойной или безошибочной
    работы на ваш устройствах и оборудовании.</string>


    <string name="music">Музыка</string>

    <integer name="com_vk_sdk_AppId">6163988</integer>
    <string name="vk_success">Картинка опубликована на вашей стене ВК</string>
    <string name="vk_error">Ошибка входа ВК</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">113293639384475</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb113293639384475</string>
    <string name="fb_success">Картинка опубликована в вашей хронике Facebook</string>
    <string name="fb_error">Ошибка входа Facebook</string>

    <string name="did_not_know">Я этого не знал</string>

    <string name="single_game">Одиночная игра</string>
    <string name="game_with_friend">Игра с другом</string>
    <string name="internet_access">Необходимо подключение к интернету</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pause">Пауза</string>
    <string name="continue_game">Продолжить</string>
    <string name="go_to_choose_category">Выбрать новую категорию</string>
    <string name="go_to_main_menu">Выйти в главное меню</string>

    <string name="harder">Усложняем!</string>

    <string name="help_1">У вас есть 5 жизней и 10 секунд на ответ \n \n Если ответите неправильно — потеряете жизнь, если не успеете ответить — потеряете жизнь</string>
    <string name="help_2">Ваша задача — набрать как можно больше очков в течении 120 секунд \n \n Если выберете неправильный ответ — жизнь не потеряете</string>
    <string name="help_3">Получить информацию о песне можно нажав на кнопку «назад» \n \n Нажав на кнопку справа вы сможете узнать информацию об авторском праве на это изображение</string>
    <string name="help_4">Удачной игры!</string>
    <string name="help_5">Далее</string>
    <string name="help_6">Закрыть</string>

    <string name="title_bar_name">Выберите категорию</string>

    <string name="game_over_1">Игра</string>
    <string name="game_over_2">окончена!</string>
    <string name="score">счёт</string>
    <string name="new_record">новый рекорд!</string>
    <string name="share">поделиться</string>
    <string name="go_screen_restart">заново</string>
    <string name="go_screen_cat">к категориям</string>
    <string name="no_more_answers_1">Вы супер!</string>
    <string name="no_more_answers_2">Вы дали 45 правильных ответов и в нашей базе данных закончились картинки для этой категории.</string>
    <string name="no_more_answers_3">Перейти на страницу результатов</string>
    <string name="no_more_answers_4">вы угадали всё!</string>

    <string name="animals">Животные</string>
    <string name="dogs">Собаки</string>
    <string name="attractions">Достопримеча-\nтельности</string>
    <string name="autos">Автомобили</string>
    <string name="devices">Устройства</string>
    <string name="historical_events">Исторические события</string>
    <string name="towns">Города</string>
    <string name="flags">Флаги и гербы</string>
    <string name="paintings">Картины</string>
    <string name="persons">Знаменитые личности</string>
    <string name="weapons">Военная техника и оружие</string>

    <string name="game_for_live">Игра на жизни</string>
    <string name="game_for_time">Игра на время</string>

    <string name="cc_attribution_1">Это изображение — изменённое</string>
    <string name="cc_attribution_2">фото</string>
    <string name="cc_attribution_3">автора</string>
    <string name="cc_attribution_4">, распространяемое под лицензией</string>
    <string name="cc_attribution_5">Показанное вам изображение также распространяется под лицензией</string>
    <string name="cc_attribution_6">автором этого приложения.</string>

    <string name="pd_attribution_1">Это изображение — изменённое</string>
    <string name="pd_attribution_2">фото</string>
    <string name="pd_attribution_3">автора</string>
    <string name="pd_attribution_4">, находящееся в общественном достоянии.</string>
    <string name="pd_attribution_5">Показанное вам изображение также отдано в общественное достояние автором этого приложения.</string>

    <string name="odbl_attribution_1">«© Участники OpenStreetMap».</string>

    <string name="custom_attribution_1"><Data><![CDATA[<a href=\'https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User:Cyrillic\'>Cyrillic</a> at the <a href=\'https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page\'>English language Wikipedia</a>]]></Data></string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_2"><Data><![CDATA[<a href=\'https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D0%A3%D1%87%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%BA:Sinodov\'>Sinodov</a> at <a href=\'https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/%D0%97%D0%B0%D0%B3%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B2%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F_%D1%81%D1%82%D1%80%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B0\'>Russian Wikipedia</a>]]></Data></string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_3">© Ad Meskens / Wikimedia Commons</string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_4">Photo: Graeme Main/MOD</string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_5"><Data><![CDATA[<a href=\'https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User:Quickload\'>Quickload</a> at <a href=\'https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page\'>English Wikipedia</a>]]></Data></string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_6"><Data><![CDATA[By: Tontan Travel <br>Link: <a href=\'www.tontantravel.com\'>www.tontantravel.com</a>]]></Data></string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_7"><Data><![CDATA[Wellcome Library, London. Wellcome Images images@wellcome.ac.uk <a href=\'http://wellcomeimages.org\'>http://wellcomeimages.org</a> A duck billed platypus (watermole). Colour lithograph after W. Kuhnert. By: Wilhelm KuhnertPublished: -
<\br>Copyrighted work available under Creative Commons Attribution only licence CC BY 4.0 <a href=\'https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/\'>https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/</a>]]></Data></string>
    <string name="custom_attribution_8">Photo by Greg Hume</string>
</resources>
